

Software Engineer

Jombang, Indonesia

085648636747

### Detail

Jombang Indonesia 085648636747 ronyelkahfi@gmail.com

# Links

https://github.com/rony elkahfi/

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/fatkhur-ronib69014b8/

# **Profesional Skills**

PHP

MySQL

Javascript

**HTML** 

CSS

Codeigniter

Laravel

**JQuery** 

GIT/CICD

Golang

Container/Docker

## Profile

I am a web developer with four six of experience. Work with PHP development environment. From native, to frameworks like Codeigniter and Laravel. I have helped small agencies to transform from traditional administration to integrated database-based administration, and have duplicated it across multiple agencies. I've also worked for an IT company to develop and maintain their cloud services.

I am interested in learning the basics about software development for good software quality and maintainability. Currently studying backend technologies such as golang, microservice, docker, CICD with a clean architecture concept.

# **Employment History**

#### Web Developer, PT. Interaktif Internasional

Jan. 2018 - Present

Develop software for internal and for cloud services. Among them are the backend for the POS system, and the attendance data management system. It has been used by several public and private companies. My job is to create features that have been defined by the company. As much as possible I create a lightweight system for user convenience, optimize database requirements, and reusable code.

#### Freelance Web Programmer, Multi Kreasindo

Nov. 2014 - Dec. 2017

Creating administrative software for several health institutions such as hospitals and clinical laboratories, my job is to explore user requirements, create simple technical diagrams, implement them into code, and maintain them. Here, I make as much software as possible to suit my clients in the field.



# Project Experiences

#### InAct Attendance Device Management System

This application is used to manage attendance data from various machines spread across various regions.

Used by PT. Aneka Indomakmur, PT. Pertani Persero, CV. Beauty Kasatama.and others.

My role was research on attendance machine communication technique, implementation of the scheme provided by the system analyst.

#### MyBilling CRM and subscription system

An application like CRM software for internal companies, to handle buyers who subscribe to the company's application services. Sending email notifications, Performing subscription renewals, and integrating with payment gateways to automatically activate user services.

Built with PHP, CI, MySQL, midtrans API, Espay, QRIS Payment Gateway, etc

#### **Employee and Payroll Management System**

A software for managing employee data, files and calculating payroll based on data from attendance machines, and several components of employee salaries

Used by Rumah Sakit Islam Jombang. My role is to develop features based on the design given by the system analyst.

#### Clinic Laboratories Management System

A system for managing clinical laboratory administration. Managing registration, queuing system, patient check-up, printing of check-up results, financial reports, taxes, and referral service fees.

Used by Laboratorium klinik Persada Jombang.

#### **Hospital Information Management System**

Management application for hospital administration for all parts of the hospital administrasion for example Polyclinic, Medical records, patient care, pharmacy, OK, VK, Pantry, Accounting, Purchasing. etc

Used by RSUD Ploso Jombang, Pelengkap Medical Center Jombang, PKU Muhammadiyah Jombang Hospital.

# Education and Course

ACP14 Back End, Alterra Academy

Dec 2021

Teknik Informatika, Universitas Darul Ulum Jombang

Sept 2012 – Sept 2016

# **Events**

#### Webinar Design Pattern 101, Alterra Academy

2022

How to design problem solver product

Workshop Backend 101-Golang, Alterra Academy

2022

Build REST API using Golang

Jatim Developers Day

2019

Facebook Developers Circle, FDC Surabaya
2017

Surabaya Developers Day, Surabaya Dev
2017

Bekraf Developers Day Surabaya
2017